(Penny:)to fix the pain you're
causing her right now?
(Sheldon:)I'm sure you're right.
(Sheldon:)I suppose I should
apologize to you, as well.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)That must have hurt watching me
look for other women
(Sheldon:)without ever even
considering you.
(Sheldon:)Please understand
that I think of you
(Sheldon:)as more of a nanny.
(Penny:)Just finish your ice cream
so I can get you home to bed.
(Raj:)I wonder if this is
what it feels like
(Raj:)to be Bernadette's baby.
(Stuart:)I don't know. Bernadette's baby
doesn't have a Jacuzzi jet
(Stuart:)hitting just the right spot.
(Howard:)Those jets are
for my secret spot, not his!
What do you do in there?!
(Howard:)It's called relaxing,
and that's all you need to know.